quackquack.in 2019-04-15

# QuackQuack.in - Online Dating Site Privacy Policy Notice

QuackQuack.in Privacy Policy

We, at Quackquack.in, take your privacy very seriously and abide by the following policy to ensure your satisfaction. If you have any concerns, please do not hesitate to [contact us](https://www.quackquack.in/v2/help/contactus.php)

**What information does Quackquack.in collect/track about me**

Quackquack's sole purpose is to assist you in finding your companion securely and privately. Whether you are seeking friendship, social networking, dating or a serious relationship, Quackquack is here to help you.

To accomplish the above purpose, our members create unique profiles (provide personal information) and our matching technology provides matches based on pre-selected criteria.

The public (visitors, users, excluding employees of Quackquack.in or Quackquack.in’s service providers or the financial institutions used to process membership charges) cannot use the information we gather to identify specific individuals.

Further, in order to facilitate commerce, might collect credit card or debit card information, member's address, or bank information only from those who choose to join Quackquack.in. Visitors to our site may browse, search and view user profiles or features without entering any personal information.

 **WHERE DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY APPLY**

This Privacy Policy applies to websites, apps, events and other services operated by Quackquack.in. For simplicity, we refer to all of these as our "services" in this Privacy Policy. To make it extra clear, we've added links to this Privacy Policy on all applicable services.

**Information we collect**  
It goes without saying, we can't help you develop meaningful connections without some information about you, such as basic profile details and the types of people you'd like to meet. We also collect information generated as you use our services, for example access logs, as well as information from third parties, like when you access our services through a social media account. If you want additional info, we go into more detail below.

**Information you give us**  
You choose to give us certain information when using our services. This includes:

When you create an account, you provide us with at least your email address, password, mobile number as well as some basic details necessary for the service to work, such as your gender and date of birth.

When you complete your profile, you can share with us additional information, such as details on your personality, lifestyle, interests and other details about you, as well as content such as photos and videos. To add certain content, like pictures or videos, you may allow us to access your camera or photo album. Some of the information you choose to provide us may be considered "special" or "sensitive" in certain jurisdictions, for example your racial or ethnic origins, sexual orientation and religious beliefs. By choosing to provide this information, you consent to our processing of that information.

When you subscribe to a paid service or make a purchase directly from us (directly or indirectly), you provide our payment service provider with information, such as your debit or credit card number or other financial information and information like your email address, phone number, address, etc.

When you participate in surveys or focus groups, you give us your insights into our products and services, responses to our questions and testimonials.

When you choose to participate in our promotions, events or contests, we collect the information that you use to register or enter.

If you contact our customer care team, we collect the information you give us during the interaction. Sometimes, we monitor or record these interactions for training purposes and to ensure a high quality of service.

If you ask us to communicate with or otherwise process information of other people (for example, if you ask us to send an email on your behalf to one of your friends), we collect the information about others that you give us in order to complete your request.

Of course, we also process your chats with other users as well as the content you publish, as part of the operation of the services.

**Information we receive from others**  
In addition to the information you provide us directly, we receive information about you from others, including:

Other Users: Other users may provide information about you as they use our services. For instance, we may collect information about you from other users if they contact us about you.

Social Media: You may be able to use your social media login (such as Facebook) to create and log into your Quackquack.in account. This saves you from having to remember a user name and password and allows you to share some information from your social media account with us.

Other: We may receive info about you from our partners, for instance where Quackquack ads are published on a partner's websites and platforms (in which case they may pass along details on a campaign's success).

**Information collected when you use our services**  
When you use our services, we collect information about which features you've used, how you've used them and the devices you use to access our services. See below for more details:

Usage Information: We collect information about your activity on our services, for instance how you use them (e.g., IP Addresses, date and time you logged in, features you've been using, searches, clicks and pages which have been shown to you, referring webpage address, advertising that you click on) and how you interact with other users (e.g., users you connect and interact with, time and date of your exchanges, number of messages you send and receive).

Device information: We collect information from and about the device(s) you use to access our services, including:

Hardware and software information such as IP address, device ID and type, device-specific and apps settings and characteristics, app crashes, advertising IDs (such as Google's AAID and Apple's IDFA), browser type, version and language, operating system, time zones, identifiers associated with cookies or other technologies that may uniquely identify your device or browser.

**Information on device sensors such as accelerometers, gyroscopes and compasses.**  
Other information with your consent: If you give us permission, we can collect your precise geolocation (latitude and longitude) through various means, depending on the service and device you're using, including GPS, Bluetooth or Wi-Fi connections. The collection of your geolocation may occur in the background even when you aren't using the services if the permission you gave us expressly permits such collection. If you decline permission for us to collect your geolocation, we will not collect it.

Similarly, if you consent, we may collect your photos and videos (for instance, if you want to publish a photo, video or streaming on the services).

 **COOKIES AND OTHER SIMILAR DATA COLLECTION TECHNOLOGIES**

We use and may allow others to use cookies and similar technologies (e.g., web beacons, pixels) to recognize you and/or your device(s). You may read our [Cookie Policy](https://www.quackquack.in/cookiepolicy) for more information on why we use them (such as authenticating you, remembering your preferences and settings, analyzing site traffic and trends, delivering and measuring the effectiveness of advertising campaigns, allowing you to use social features) and how you can better control their use, through your browser settings and other tools.

Some web browsers (including Safari, Internet Explorer, Firefox and Chrome) have a "Do Not Track" (" DNT") feature that tells a website that a user does not want to have his or her online activity tracked. If a website that responds to a DNT signal receives a DNT signal, the browser can block that website from collecting certain information about the browser's user. Not all browsers offer a DNT option and DNT signals are not yet uniform. For this reason, many businesses, including Quackquack.in, do not currently respond to DNT signals.

 **HOW WE USE INFORMATION**

The main reason we use your information is to deliver and improve our services. Additionally, we use your info to help keep you safe and to provide you with advertising that may be of interest to you. Read on for a more detailed explanation of the various reasons we use your information, together with practical examples.

**To administer your account and provide our services to you**

Create and manage your account

Provide you with customer support and respond to your requests

Complete your transactions

Communicate with you about our services, including order management and billing

**To help you connect with other users**

Analyze your profile and that of other users to recommend meaningful connections

Show users' profiles to one another

**To ensure a consistent experience when you use our services on multiple devices**

Link the various devices you use so that you can enjoy a consistent experience of our services on all of them. We do this by linking devices and browser data, such as when you log into your account on different devices or by using partial or full IP address, browser version and similar data about your devices to help identify and link them.

**To serve you relevant offers and ads**

Administer sweepstakes, contests, discounts or other offers

Develop, display and track content and advertising tailored to your interests on our services and other sites

Communicate with you by email, phone, social media or mobile device about products or services that we think may interest you

**To improve our services and develop new ones**

Administer focus groups and surveys

Conduct research and analysis of users' behavior to improve our services and content (for instance, we may decide to change the look and feel or even substantially modify a given feature based on users' behavior)

Develop new features and services

**To prevent, detect and fight fraud or other illegal or unauthorized activities**

Address ongoing or alleged misbehavior on and off-platform

Perform data analysis to better understand and design countermeasures against these activities

Retain data related to fraudulent activities to prevent against recurrences

**To ensure legal compliance**

Comply with legal requirements

Assist law enforcement

Enforce or exercise our rights, for example our Terms

**To process your information as described above, we rely on the following legal bases:**

Provide our service to you: Most of the time, the reason we process your information is to perform the contract that you have with us.

Legitimate interests: We may use your information where we have legitimate interests to do so. For instance, we analyze users' behavior on our services to continuously improve our offerings and we process information for administrative, fraud detection and other legal purposes.

Consent: From time to time, we may ask for your consent to use your information for certain specific reasons. You may withdraw your consent at any time by [contacting us](https://www.quackquack.in/v2/help/contactus.php)

 **HOW WE SHARE INFORMATION**

Since our goal is to help you make meaningful connections, the main sharing of users' information is, of course, with other users. We also share some users' information with service providers and partners who assist us in operating and or improving the services, with other products in our company and, in some cases, legal authorities. Read on for more details about how your information is shared with others.

With other users: You share information with other users when you voluntarily disclose information on the service (including your public profile). Please be careful with your information and make sure that the content you share is stuff that you're comfortable being publicly viewable since neither you nor we can control what others do with your information once you share it.

If you choose to limit the audience for all or part of your profile or for certain content or information about you, then it will be visible according to your settings available on Quackquack.in.

With our service providers and partners: We use third parties to help us operate and improve our services. These third parties assist us with various tasks, including data hosting and maintenance, analytics, customer care, marketing, advertising, moderation, payment processing, optimizations and security operations.

We may also share information with partners who distribute and assist us in advertising our services. For instance, we may share limited information on you in hashed, non-human readable form to advertising partners.

We follow a process when engaging with any service provider or working with any partner whom we can trust. Our service providers and partners must agree to strict confidentiality obligations. However, in some cases where we use certain SaaS services, APIs or similar services, there may not be limited confidentiality obligations.

For corporate transactions: We may transfer your information if we are involved, whether in whole or in part, in a merger, sale, acquisition, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or other change of ownership or control.

When required by law: We may disclose your information if reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with a legal process, such as a court order, subpoena or search warrant, government / law enforcement investigation or other legal requirements; (ii) to assist in the prevention or detection of crime (subject in each case to applicable law); or (iii) to protect the safety of any person.

To enforce legal rights: We may also share information: (i) if disclosure would mitigate our liability in an actual or threatened lawsuit; (ii) as necessary to protect our legal rights and legal rights of our users, business partners or other interested parties; (iii) to enforce our agreements with you; and (iv) to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing.

We may use and share non-personal information (meaning information that, by itself, does not identify who you are such as device information, general demographics, general behavioral data, geolocation in de-identified form), as well as personal information in hashed, non-human readable form, under any of the above circumstances. We may also share this information with third parties (notably advertisers) to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our services and on websites or applications of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine this information with additional non-personal information or personal information in hashed, non-human readable form collected from other sources. More information on our use of cookies and similar technologies can be found in our Cookie Policy.

 **YOUR RIGHTS**

We want you to be in control of your information, so we have provided you with the following tools:

Access / Update tools in the service: account settings that help you to access, rectify or delete information that you provided to us and that's associated with your account directly within the service. If you have any question on those tools and settings, please contact our [customer care](https://www.quackquack.in/v2/help/contactus.php). However, some information cannot be modified and is required for record keeping.

Device permissions: Mobile platforms have permission systems for specific types of device data and notifications, such as phone book and location services as well as push notifications. You can change your settings on your device to either consent or oppose the collection of the corresponding information or the display of the corresponding notifications. Of course, if you do that, certain services may lose full functionality.

Deletion: You can deactivate your account by using the corresponding ‘Deactivate’ functionality directly on the service or you can contact us to ‘Suspend/Delete’ your account. However, ‘Deactivating’ or ‘Suspending’ or ‘Deleting’ your account will only remove your profile from other user’s view. Your information may however, show on certain search results. We also keep your information for record keeping.

Keep in mind, we may reject requests for certain reasons, including if the request is unlawful or if it may infringe on trade secrets or intellectual property or the privacy of another user. 

Also, we may not be able to accommodate certain requests to object to the processing of personal information, notably where such requests would not allow us to provide our service to you anymore. For instance, we cannot provide our service if we do not have your date of birth.

Uninstall: You can stop all information collection by an app by uninstalling it using the standard uninstall process for your device. If you uninstall the app from your mobile device, the unique identifier associated with your device will continue to be stored. If you re-install the application on the same mobile device, we will be able to re-associate this identifier to your previous transactions and activities.

 **HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**

We work hard to protect you from unauthorized access to or alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information. As with all technology companies, although we take steps to secure your information, we do cannot guarantee, and you should not expect, that your personal information will always remain secure. We cannot be held liable if your information gets ‘hacked’ and if it is leaked or gets public.

We regularly monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and regularly review our information collection, storage and processing practices to update our physical, technical and organizational security measures.

We may suspend your use of all or part of the services without notice if we suspect or detect any breach of security. If you believe that your account or information is no longer secure, please notify us immediately by [contacting us](https://www.quackquack.in/v2/help/contactus.php).

In order to ensure that our systems and your information are protected against unauthorized access, theft and loss, we implemented a bug bounty program. For more information about our bug bounty program, you can [contact us](https://www.quackquack.in/v2/help/contactus.php).

 **HOW LONG WE RETAIN YOUR INFORMATION**

We keep your personal information only as long as we need it for legitimate business purposes. In practice, we do not delete or anonymize your information of your account because:

We must keep it to evidence our compliance with applicable law (for instance, records of consents to our Terms, Privacy Policy and other similar consents)

There is an outstanding issue, claim or dispute requiring us to keep the relevant information until it is resolved; or

The information must be kept for our legitimate business interests, such as fraud prevention and enhancing users' safety and security. For example, information may need to be kept to prevent a user who was banned for unsafe behavior or security incidents from opening a new account.

 **CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Our services are restricted to users who are 18 years of age or older. We do not permit users under the age of 18 on our platform and we do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you suspect that a user is under the age of 18, please [contact us](https://www.quackquack.in/v2/help/contactus.php).

 **PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES**

Because we're always looking for new and innovative ways to help you build meaningful connections, this policy may change over time. We may or may not notify changes to specific privacy policy changes.

 **HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, you can [contact us](https://www.quackquack.in/v2/help/contactus.php)
